RG 015, Office of Policy and Management
Connecticut State Library
- Series 12. Planning and Budgeting, circa 1971-1972; 2004-026; 22 cubic feet
  - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, 1971-1972
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 2 (Box 9)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 10)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 10)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 and No. 2 (Box 10)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 and No. 2, Vol. 1 (Box 10)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 and No. 2, Vol. 2 (Box 10)
    - Appendix, B, Millstone Unit No. 1 and No. 2, Vol. 3 (Box 10)
    - Addendum 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 and No. 2 (Box 10)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 10)
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 2 (Box 10)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 11)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage (Box 11)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 11)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operating License Stage, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 11)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 11)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volumes 1-3 (Box 11)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 11)
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 2 (Box 11)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 12)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Amendment No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 12)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage (Box 12)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 12)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operating License stage, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 12)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No.; 2 (Box 12)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volumes 1-3 (Box 12)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 12)
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 12)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 13)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit 2, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage (Box 13)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Amendment No. 1, Environmental Report, Operating License Stage (Box 13)
    - Addendum No. 1 to Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 13)
    - Addendum No. 2 to Environmental Report, Operationg License Stage, Appendixes, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 13)
    - Appendix A, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2 (Box 13)
    - Appendix B, Millstone Unit No. 1 & No. 2, Volumes 1-3 (Box 13)
    - Appendix C, Millstone Unit No. 1 (Box 13)
    - Appendix D, Millstone Unit No. 2 (Box 13)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station Unit No. 3, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage, Docket No. 50-423, 4 copies (Box 14)
    - Amendment No. 1, 4 copies (Box 14)
    - Addendum No. 1, 4 copies (Box 14)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station Unit No. 3, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage, Docket No. 50-423, 4 copies (Box 15)
    - Amendment No. 1, 3 copies (Box 15)
    - Addendum No. 1, 3 copies (Box 15)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 3, Environmental Report, Construction Stage Permit, Vol. 1-2 (Box 16)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 3, Environmental Report, Construction Permit Stage, Docket No. 50-423 (Box 17)
    - Amendment No. 1 (Box 17)
    - Addendum No. 1 (Box 17)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Amendment No. 3, Docket No. 50-423, 20 copies (Box 17)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Appendix A, 3 copies (Box 17)
    - Millstone Nuclear Power Station, Unit No. 3, Appendix A, 7 copies (Box 18)
    - Addendum 3 to Environmental Report, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1, Docket No. 50-245 and Millstone Unit No. 2 Docket No. 50-336, Operating License Stage, Millstone Unit NO. 3, Construction Permit Stage, 3 copies (Box 18)
    - Addendum 3 to Environmental Report, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1, Docket No. 50-245, Millstone Unit No. 1, Docket No. 50-336, Operating License Stage, Millstone Unit No. 3, Construction Permit Stage, 8 copies (Box 19)
    - Addendum No. 4 to Environmental Report, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1, Docket No. 50-245, Millstone Unit No. 1, Docket No. 50-336, Operating License Stage, Millstone Unit No. 3, Construction Permit Stage, 11 copies (Box 20)
    - Addendum No. 5 to Environmental Report, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1 Docket No. 40-245, Millstone Unit No. 2 Docket No. 50-336, Operating License Stage, Millstone Unit No. 3 Docket No. 50-423, Construction Permit Stage, 14 copies (Box 21)
    - Addendum No. 5 to Environmental Report, Appendices, Millstone Unit No. 1, Docket No. 50-245, Millstone Unit No. 2, Docket No. 50-336, Operating License Stage, Millstone Unit No. 3, Docket No. 50-423, Construction Permit Stage, 6 copies (Box 22)
- Series 13. Comprehensive Planning Division, 1957-1991; 28 cubic feet
  - Community Development Block Grants, 1970-1977
    - 1970-1976, 1985-026B
      Preapplication review records for Title IV and discretionary grants to non-metropolitan areas.
      - PNRS 161: State Police Dept., Computerization of criminal intelligence files (Box 1)
      - PNRS 162: State Police Dept., Study of Conn. police teletype system (Box 1)
      - PNRS 163: DOT, Bureau of Planning & Research, Realignment of a section of Route 25 (Box 1)
      - PNRS 164: Newtown Housing for the Elderly, Inc. (Box 1)
      - PNRS 165: Town of Newtown, Sanitary sewer system, primary & secondary treatment (Box 1)
      - PNRS 166: Town of Essex, Open space acq. (Box 1)
      - PNRS 167: DOT, Widening of Route 73, Watertown (Box 1)
      - PNRS 168: DOT: Realignment of Route 108, Shelton (Box 1)
      - PNRS 169: DOT, Relocation of Route 22, North Haven (Box 1)
      - PNRS 170: Wheeler Clinic, Inc., Plainville (Box 1)
      - PNRS 171: DOT, Realignment of Route 6, Hampton and Brooklyn (Box 1)
      - PNRS 172: DOT, Widening of S.R. 502 in East Hartford and Manchester (Box 1)
      - PNRS 173: Vernon sewer construction (Box 1)
      - PNRS 174: ANR, Watershed protection & flood prevention in North Canaan, Canaan, Norfolk, Goshen and Cornwall (Box 1)
      - PNRS 175: ANR, Addition to Mattatuck State Forest (Box 1)
      - PNRS 176: ANR, Addition to Haddam Meadows State Park (Box 1)
      - PNRS 177: ANR, Addition to Gillette Castle State Park (Box 1)
      - PNRS 178: Shelton, Sewer interceptors, pumping station, sewage treatment plant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 179: Stonington, Sewage treatment facilities (Box 1)
      - PNRS 180: Westport, Sewerage & sewage treatment facilities (Box 1)
      - PNRS 181: DOT, Reconstruction of Basset Road in North Haven (Box 1)
      - PNRS 182: TOPICS study in Hamden (Box 1)
      - PNRS 183: TOPICS study in New Haven (Box 1)
      - PNRS 184: TOPICS study in New London (Box 1)
      - PNRS 185: TOPICS study in North Haven (Box 1)
      - PNRS 186: TOPICS study in Hartford (Box 1)
      - PNRS 187: TOPICS study in Bridgeport (Box 1)
      - PNRS 188: Southington, Additions to Water pollution control plant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 189: Harbor Brook sewer & pumping stations (Box 1)
      - PNRS 190: Dept. of Mental Health, Sewage treatment plant at Fairfield Hills Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 191: Mental Health, Addition & improvements to sewage plant at Mansfield School & Hospital (Box 1)
      - 192: Hamden, Open space acq. & development to Brooksvale Park (Box 1)
      - PNRS 193: Hamden, Open space acq. & development (Box 1)
      - PNRS 195: East Hampton Water & Sewer Authority (Box 1)
      - PNRS 196: Addition to Quinebaug River Hatchery in Plainfield (Box 1)
      - PNRS 197: Derby Public Library (Box 1)
      - PNRS 182: TOPICS study in Hamden (Box 1)
      - PNRS 198: North Haven Public Library (Box 1)
      - PNRS 199: Hartford Police Dept., Regional law enforcement planning for 1971 (Box 1)
      - PNRS 200: New Haven Dept. of Police Service, Law enforcement planning assistance (Box 1)
      - PNRS 201: South Central Connecticut Comprehensive Health Planning, Inc., Comprehensive health planning (Box 1)
      - PNRS 202: Relocation of Route 5, East Hartford and South Windsor (Box 1)
      - PNRS 203: CNVRPA, Law enforcement planning grant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 204: DOT, TOPICS project in New London re Jefferson Ave. & Chester St. (Box 1)
      - PNRS 205: CNVRPA, 701 planning grant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 206: SECRPA, 701 planning grant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 207: Criminal Justice Supervisory Board, Law enforcement project (Box 1)
      - PNRS 208: CCRPA, Law enforcement project (Box 1)
      - PNRS 209: CCRPA, 701 assistance grant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 210: City of Waterbury (Box 1)
      - PNRS 211: Easter Seal Goodwill Industries Rehabilitation Center (Box 1)
      - PNRS 212: Bristol Hospital, Inc. (Box 1)
      - PNRS 213: Mill Health Center (Box 1)
      - PNRS 214: St. Mary's Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 215: Griffin Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 216: St. Joseph's Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 217: Community Health Care Center Plan, Inc. (Box 1)
      - PNRS 218: Johnson Memorial Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 219: William W. Backus Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 220: Hospital of St. Raphael (Box 1)
      - PNRS 221: City of Hartford Health Department (Box 1)
      - PNRS 222: Milford, Board of Sewer Commissioners (Box 1)
      - PNRS 223: Lawrence and Memorial Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 224: Manchester Memorial Hospital (Box 1)
      - PNRS 225: Stamford Health Department (Box 1)
      - PNRS 226: Pequot Library (Box 1)
      - PNRS 227: ANR, Acq. in Plainfield (Box 1)
      - PNRS 228: Sewer Authority, Town of Darien (Box 1)
      - PNRS 229: DOT, Improvement of Route 8 (Box 1)
      - PNRS 230: OSP, Non-metropolitan districts 701 grant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 231: South Windsor, Sanitary sewers (Box 1)
      - PNRS 232: DOT, Relocation of Route 25 in Monroe and Newtown (Box 1)
      - PNRS 233: DOT, Planning along Route 2 in Marlborough and Colchester (Box 1)
      - PNRS 234: Statewide planning grant (Box 1)
      - PNRS 235: GBRPH, HUD 701 (Box 1)
      - PNRS 236: Bethel, Water supply and distribution system (Box 1)
      - PNRS 237: Boulevard Bridge (Route 40) over railroad tracks in New Haven (Box 1)
      - PNRS 238: DOT, Extension of Route 9 in Berlin and Cromwell (Box 1)
      - PNRS 239: CRPA, HUD 701 (Box 1)
      - PNRS 240: DCA, HUD 701 (Box 1)
      - PNRS 241: Norwich Community Development Corp., Industrial park development (Box 1)
      - PNRS 242: TSTC, Urban mass transportation program & regional systems and planning study (Box 1)
      - PNRS 243: ANR, Addition to Miller's Pond State Park (Box 1)
      - PNRS 244: ANR, Addition to Meshomasic State Forest (Box 1)
      - PNRS 245: ANR, Addition to Cockaponset State Park (Box 1)
      - PNRS 246: ANR, Addition to Mt. Tom State Park (Box 2)
      - PNRS 247: ANR, Addition to Nye-Holman State Forest (Box 2)
      - PNRS 248: Addition to Wopowog Management Area (Box 2)
      - PNRS 249: Rail-Bus demonstration project (Box 2)
      - PNRS 250: City of Bristol, Collection system (Box 2)
      - PNRS 251: Old Saybrook, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 252: United Community Services, Areawide comprehensive health planning (Box 2)
      - PNRS 253: Capitol Region Council of Governments, solid waste demonstration grant (Box 2)
      - PNRS 254: Valley Council of Governments, Urban mass transit demonstration (Box 2)
      - PNRS 255: Highway planning work program (Box 2)
      - PNRS 256: DOT, Capital grant for urban mass transportation (Box 2)
      - 257: City of Norwalk, Acq. of Grassy Island (Box 2)
      - PNRS 258: SWRPA, Comprehensive planning (Box 2)
      - PNRS 259: Bridgeport Municipal Airport (Box 2)
      - PNRS 260: City of Bristol, Sewer (Box 2)
      - PNRS 261: Society to Advance the Retarded, Inc., Norwalk (Box 2)
      - PNRS 262: Danbury, Construction of outfall sewer (Box 2)
      - PNRS 263: Farmington, Open space acquisition (Box 2)
      - PNRS 264: Branford, Sewerage system (Box 2)
      - PNRS 265: City of Norwich, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 266: Berlin, Development in Timberlane Park (Box 2)
      - PNRS 268: TSTC, Urban mass transportation technical study, Connecticut (Box 2)
      - PNRS 269: TSTC, Urban mass transportation technical study, New York (Box 2)
      - PNRS 270: Town of South Windsor, Interceptor sewer (Box 2)
      - PNRS 271: Military Dept., Contingency operational planning (state & local) (Box 2)
      - PNRS 272: Manchester, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 273: DOT, Interstate 84 (Project #77-113) (Box 2)
      - PNRS 274: Carefree Homeowners Association, Inc., Community water system (Box 2)
      - PNRS 275: TSTC, Special project, Comprehensive planning assistance (Box 2)
      - PNRS 276: Bridgeport Municipal Airport, New rotating beacon (Box 2)
      - PNRS 277: ANR, Acq. in Pomfret and Putnam (Box 2)
      - PNRS 278: Monroe (Conservation & Water Resources Commission), Wagner Tract (Box 2)
      - PNRS 279: Clinton, Urban beautification (Box 2)
      - PNRS 280: Clinton, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 281: Torrington, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 282: Monroe Recreational Authority, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 283: Monroe Recreational Authority (Box 2)
      - PNRS 284: Town of Guilford (Box 2)
      - PNRS 285: Dept. of Navy (New London), Land acquisition (Box 2)
      - PNRS 286: New Haven, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 287: Windsor, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 288: DOT, Interstate 95 (Box 2)
      - PNRS 289: UMTA, DOT Westchester County, New York (Box 2)
      - PNRS 290: City of Meriden, Parks & Recreation HUD open space (Box 2)
      - PNRS 291: Plymouth, Interceptor sewer (Box 2)
      - PNRS 292: DOT, Interstate 86 in Vernon, Tolland, Willington, Ashford, Union (Box 2)
      - PNRS 293: DOT, Route 25 in Litchfield (Box 2)
      - PNRS 294: DCA, Technical assistance program (Box 2)
      - PNRS 295: Interstate 95 and Route 32 in New London (Box 2)
      - PNRS 296: Town of Groton, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 297: DOT, Relocation of Route 10 in Southington (Box 2)
      - PNRS 298 City of New London, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 299: Stratford, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 300: DOT, Realignment of Route 58 in Bethel (Box 2)
      - PNRS 301: Weston, Open space acq. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 302: Community Progress, Inc., Community action program (Box 2)
      - PNRS 303: Health Dept., Comprehensive plan for solid waste management in Connecticut (Box 2)
      - PNRS 304: Litchfield, Relief storm water sewers (Box 2)
      - PNRS 305: Norwalk-Stamford-Danbury Regional Legal Services, Inc., Legal services (Box 2)
      - PNRS 306: RPASCC, HUD 701 grant (Box 2)
      - PNRS 307: DOT, Stonington Route 78 (Box 2)
      - PNRS 308: Interstate Sanitation Commission (Box 2)
      - PNRS 309: DOT, Improvement of Route 68 in Wallingford (Box 2)
      - PNRS 310: Historical Commission, Acq., restoration & development of Viet's Tavern (Box 2)
      - PNRS 311: Historical Commission, Field survey (Box 2)
      - PNRS 312: Farmington, Sanitary sewer construction (Box 2)
      - PNRS 313: Community Action for Greater Middletown, Inc. (Box 2)
      - PNRS 314: Comprehensive Planning Program (Urban Planning Assistance)TSTC (Box 2)
      - PNRS 315: Urban mass transportation technical study, Newark Airport access study (Box 2)
      - PNRS 316: Comprehensive water and related land resource planning (Box 2)
      - PNRS 317: Stamford, Open space land program, HUD (Box 2)
      - PNRS 318: Yale-New Haven Hospital, New construction, Hill-Harris Program, HEW (Box 2)
      - PNRS 319: Yale-New Haven Hospital, Alteration, Hill-Harris Program, HEW (Box 2)
      - PNRS 320: Yale-New Haven Hospital, Addition & alteration, Hill-Harris Program, HEW (Box 2)
      - PNRS 321: Study of water supply for SECRPA (Box 2)
      - PNRS 322: Simsbury, Waste water treatment plant (Box 2)
      - PNRS 323: Northeast Model Cities Citizens' Union training & technical assistance (Box 2)
      - PNRS 324: CNVRPA, Comprehensive areawide health planning (Box 2)
      - PNRS 325: Avon, Construction of interceptor sewers & appurtenances (Box 2)
      - 326: Reconstruction at Danbury Municipal Airport (runways) (Box 3)
      - PNRS 327: Vernon, HUD open space (Box 3)
      - PNRS 328: Stamford, CAP 81 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 319: TSTC HUD 701 Special project minority training work/study program (Box 3)
      - PNRS 330: OEO-Danbury, Adult education program for Spanish-speaking adults (Box 3)
      - PNRS 331: Torrington, To develop land for industrial park (Box 3)
      - PNRS 332: Town of Enfield, Construction of trunk and lateral sewers (Box 3)
      - PNRS 333: LHRPA, Regional solid waste transportation & site depletion planning study (Box 3)
      - PNRS 334: DOT, Realignment of 0.71 mile of Route 289 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 335: Community Action Committee of Danbury, Summer Head Start in Bethel, Newtown, New Milford (Box 3)
      - PNRS 336: Community Action Committee of Danbury, Year round Head Start (Box 3)
      - PNRS 337: City of Bristol, Sewage collection system & water distribution (Box 3)
      - PNRS 338: DOT, Upgrade a section of Interstate 84 in Newtown and Southbury (Box 3)
      - PNRS 339: DOT, Relocation of Route 10 in Plainville and Farmington (Box 3)
      - PNRS 340: ANR (Water Resources Commission), State Water Pollution Control Program (Box 3)
      - PNRS 341: DOT, Relocation of Route 72 in Bristol (Box 3)
      - PNRS 342: Health Planning Council, Comprehensive health planning (Box 3)
      - PNRS 343: Town of North Haven, HUD Water & sewer installation of sewers (Box 3)
      - PNRS 344: City of Stamford, Water & sewer, HUD and FWQA (Box 3)
      - PNRS 345: Establishment of Resource & Development Project in Western Connecticut (Box 3)
      - PNRS 346: Restoration of Wethersfield Cove Warehouse for future maritime museum (Box 3)
      - PNSR 347: Installation of sewer line in New Haven Ave. (Route 34) (Box 3)
      - PNRS 348: Realignment of 1.01 mile of Routes 83 and 94 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 349: Improvement of Route 69 from Clark Road to the Sargent River Bridge (Box 3)
      - PNRS 350: Relocation of Route 66 and Route 10 (SR597) (Box 3)
      - PNRS 351: Water Pollution Control Program pertaining to interstate waters of New England (Box 3)
      - PNRS 352: Acquisition of 20 acres on Middletown Ave. Wethersfield for open space (Box 3)
      - PNRS 353: Acquisition of 10 acres of land off Ridge Rd. for animal & bird sanctuary (Box 3)
      - PNRS 354: Norwalk-Wilton, Residential Addict Community, Storefront facility for pre-addicts (Box 3)
      - PNRS 355: To carry on regional planning activities in annual work program and SCC (Box 3)
      - PNRS 356: Law enforcement assistance 1972 planning grant (Box 3)
      - PNRS 357: Improvement of Conn. Route 82 from Route 52 to Ann St. (Box 3)
      - PNRS 358: Rest area on I-91 in Wallingford (southbound direction) (Box 3)
      - PNRS 359: Construction program for Watertown Fire District (Box 3)
      - PNRS 360: Development of Info to assist mental health clinics in family treatment (Box 3)
      - PNRS 361: Reconstruction of 2.8+ miles of Interstate 86 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 362-H: Construction of 182 units of low & moderate income housing on Blue Hills Ave. (Box 3)
      - PNRS 363-H: Mortgage loan for construction of 270 low & moderate income housiung units in South Arsenal neighborhood (Box 3)
      - PNRS 364-H: Mortgage loan for construction of 342 low & moderate housing units in South Arsenal neighborhood, HUD (Box 3)
      - PNRS 365: Model cities comprehensive programs in select neighborhoods in Hartford (Box 3)
      - PNRS 366: An economic upgrading program for migrant & seasonal farm workers (Box 3)
      - PNRS 367: Tweed-New Haven Airport, Ramp improvements (reconstruction & enlargement) (Box 3)
      - PNRS 368: Instrument landing system for Tweed-New Haven Airport (Box 3)
      - PNRS 369-H: Plainfield Garden Apartments (Box 3)
      - PNRS 370-H: New Milford Interfaith Housing Corp. (Box 3)
      - PNRS 371-H: Green Valley Developers, Inc., Flanders Green Section 1 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 372-H: Green Valley Developers, Inc., Flanders Green Section 2 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 373-H: Green Valley Developers, Inc., Flanders Green Section 3 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 374: Reconstruction of 1.8+ miles of Interstate 86 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 375: Relocation of Interstate 84 (Box 3)
      - PNRS 376: Willimantic, Construction of water transmission line, treatment & pumping plant & lagoon (Box 3)
      - PNRS 377: Seymour, Construction of interceptor sewer system (Box 3)
      - PNRS 378: Beacon Falls, Installation of sewer system (Box 3)
      - PNRS 379: Beacon Falls, Installation of sewers in Pines Bridge Road (Box 3)
      - PNRS 380-H: Wintergreen Associates HUD (Box 3)
      - PNRS 381: Naugatuck, Acquisition of .5 acres for spillway for recreation area (Box 3)
      - PNRS 382: To create, establish & designate a statewide scenic highway system in Connecticut (Box 3)
      - PNRS 383: ANR, Watershed protection and flood prevention planning study (Box 3)
      - PNRS 384: Chester, To abate pollution of Pattaconk Brook (Box 3)
      - PNRS 385: Recruitment & training program of minority members for planning profession at college graduate level (Box 3)
      - PNRS 386: Torrington, Construction of two public parks (Box 3)
      - PNRS 387: ABCD, Inc. (Box 3)
      - PNRS 388: Addition to Meshomasic State Forest of 47.9 acres known as "Montstream" (Box 3)
      - PNRS 389: Danbury Aviation Comm., To provide assistance in identifying runway ends & circulating guidance (Box 3)
      - PNRS 390: Replacement of Route 59 bridge over Penn Central Railroad & approaches (Box 3)
      - PNRS 391: Norwalk, To provide open space facilities to serve low-income citizens in built-up area (Box 3)
      - PNRS 392: Construction of Berlin interceptor sewer & East Berlin meter pits & connections (Box 3)
      - PNRS 393: Woodbridge, Acquisition of Bishop Estate West (Box 3)
      - PNRS 394: Enfield, Construction of water and sewer lines in Memorial Industrial Park (Box 3)
      - PNRS 395: Action for Bridgeport Community Development (Grantee), Legal services (Box 3)
      - PNRS 396: New Opportunities for Waterbury, Inc. legal services (Box 4)
      - PNRS 397: To demonstrate the implementation of the State Solid Waste Management Plan (Box 4)
      - PNRS 398: Opportunities for Waterbury, Inc. OEO Cap 81 (Box 4)
      - PNRS 399: Widening & Resurfacing of Route 110 in Stratford (Box 4)
      - PNRS 400: Realignment of Route 162 in Milford (Box 4)
      - PNRS 401-H: New Samaritan Corp./New Horizon Developments, Inc. (HUD Mortgage loan) (Box 4)
      - PNRS 402: Construction of primary feeder water mains, Norwich-EDA (Box 4)
      - PNRS 403: Feasibility study of mini-bus service for Westport (Box 4)
      - PNRS 404-H: Nutmeg Village Section 1 (Box 4)
      - PNRS 405: Construction of public works garage in Enfield (Box 4)
      - PNRS 406: Construction of solid waste facility in Bristol (Box 4)
      - PNRS 407-H: ConnVal Development Corporation HUD-Mortgage (Box 4)
      - PNRS 408: To increase & improve Winsted water system (Box 4)
      - PNRS 409: To extend sanitary sewerage system in Hamden (Box 4)
      - PNRS 410: Reconstruction of portions of Country Club Rd., Middle St., & Boardman Lane, Middletown (Box 4)
      - CDA 7511CD01: Middletown North End Project Improvement (City of Middletown) (Box 4)
      - CDA 7512CD01: CDA discretionary grant (Town of Lisbon) (Box 4)